妖女前情提要
Previously on Lost Girl...
我不会信任你的
I'll never trust you.
我似乎把Rainer的灵魂给了血圣
I may have given Rainer's soul to the blood king
在大反叛之后
after the great rebellion.
Rainer的亡灵是冲你来的
Rainer's revenants are after you.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
我爱你
I love you.
谁来帮帮我
Please,anybody!
Bo 你在哪
Bo,where are you?
把Hale救回来啊
Now bring back Hale.
不，我不能失去你
No.I can't lose you.
我不会原谅你的
I will never forgive you.
我从未给Hale道过再见
I never said goodbye to Hale.
总是待会见
It was always "see ya later"
回聊 或者什么也不说
"talk to you" or nothing at all.
就只是老朋友间交换个眼神
Just that look between old friends that says
表示我们很快就会再见面
"we'll be together again,soon"
他是个复杂的人
He was a man of complexities
既现代又传统
a traditionalist with a modern style.
年纪不小，却有着新生儿般的乐观
An old soul with the optimism of one just born.
扎莫拉族的Hale Santiago选择了他自己的人生
Hale Santiago of Clan Zamora forged his own path.
他成为了一名警察
He became a cop.
他喜欢被人叫做警察
And he liked being called a cop.
他帮人即不先入为主也无期许
He befriended without judgment or expectation.
他爱得也无拘无束
And he loved without bounds.
Hale家族里最亲近的人
As Hale's closest clan members sit
坐在他遗体旁边安静的哀悼
with his body in silent mourning...
我们开始这默哀之日
so we begin the Day of Silence
向我们亲爱的远去的海妖致敬
where we pay reverence to our dear and departed Siren.
我觉得我想尖叫
I think I might scream.
怎样都可以，Kenzi
Whatever you need,Kenzi.
我要他活着
I needed him alive.
一切都会好起来的
It will get better.
会的
It will.
我保证
I promise.
或许还会这样持续很久
Maybe not for a long time.
但是我会在你身边
But,I will be there for you.
我是你的
I am yours.
我是Raina骑士团的骑士
I am a Knight from the Order of Raina.
我宣誓效忠
And I pledge my fealty.
我的皇后
To my Queen.
向你效忠
To you.
啊果然
Uh,of course.
等等，Kenzi等等
Wait,Kenzi,wait.
我们从哪开始呢，我的殿下
Where do we begin, my liege?
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi 李夹碎
精校：潜行的五 李夹碎    压制：Searchjoy
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x12 - "Origin"
你说你是来见我的
So you say you're here to see me.
我刚好赶上，路上还被袭击了
I arrived just in time, I was attacked on my way here.
被谁
Attacked by whom?
不想让我传递讯息的人
Someone who would not want me to deliver my message.
我的皇后，你身处危险之中
You are in danger, My Queen.
我会保护你，在你身边战斗
I am here to protect you, and to fight by your side.
自从战争后我就没见过这些了
I haven't seen these since the battlefield.
真是好久以前了
It's been a long time.
听着，我不认识你
Look,I don't know you
我也不知道你在说什么
and I don't know what you're talking about,
但我知道我不是什么鬼皇后
but I do know that I'm not your Queen.
你可以退下了
So you can be dismissed.
我说的是致命的危险
I am talking about mortal danger.
好吧，我们刚从葬礼回来，你懂？
Okay, we just got back from a funeral. Do you get that?
要是你不关注我的信息将会有更多人死去
There will be more funerals if you do not heed my message.
预言说Una Mens之死
It was foretold that with the death of the Una Mens
会造成Pyrippus的复活
the Pyrippus would rise.
他在寻找你，看吧
It is you he seeks. Here.
他将复活，找寻她，那个淫妖，那唯一的人
"He shall rise and seek Her out,The Succubus,The One."
他要干嘛
What does he want?
这我可不知道
To that information, I am not privy.
预言说Una Mens被杀
The prophecy says the slaying of the Una Mens
也创造了那起源之种的力量
also creates the power of The Origin Seed...
Dyson，不是现在
Not now Dyson.
预言还说，时间已经不多
The prophecy says there is very little time.
听着，老娘对预言，种子，还有什么Pyrippus可没兴趣
Look. I don't give a shit about prophecies or seeds or Pyrippuses.
我的家人需要我
This is my family. And they need me.
Kenzi
Kenzi.
Bo 我们得去找他
Bo we have to get him.
他必须死
He has to die.
他会付出代价的 我保证
He will pay.I promise.
茵陈，蓖麻油，再撒上一点点胡椒
Wormwood, castor oil...yes and just a sprinkle of pepper.
哎呀，看看是谁来了
Well well well, look what the puss dragged in.
你在找什么吗
Looking for something?
这上面还有Hale的血
It still has Hale's blood.
当我割破你喉咙的时候，就当是我俩一起问候你吧
So when I slit your throat, think of it as a gift from us both.
你不是真来杀我的吧
You didn't really just come here to kill me did you?
不然呢
Why else?
你知道吗，作为非人类来说
You know, for supernatural creatures and all that
你们对即将要发生的事还真是知之甚少
you guys don't know shit about what's going on in your own lives.
你大概不知道Rainer会死吧
I suppose you know nothing about Rainer dying.
很快
And soon too.
Rainer怎么了
What about Rainer?
流浪者复活时，另一个诅咒将会降临于他
When the Wanderer rises another curse shall befall him
诅咒若不解除，七日之内他必死无疑
and in 7 days he will expire unless the curse is broken.
这都写在你们的历史里，白痴
It's in your history,moron.
扎莫拉圣枝在哪
Where is the twig of Zamora?
神啊你可真烦
Oh god you are so annoying.
你知道吗，我给他一刀算是帮了他大忙
You know, I did Hale a solid when I drove that sword into him.
否则，要和你这种可悲、脆弱的人类
Can you imagine the disappointment that he would have
在一起一辈子
eventually felt,knowing that he was forever bound
最后他得有多失望啊
to your pathetic,weak,human ass.
你还知道Rainer的什么
What else do you know about Rainer?
这里一点那里一点咯
A little of this and a little of that.
说
Tell me!
你会眼睁睁看着你朋友死去，却束手无策
You will watch friends die and do nothing about it.
我们还不能杀他
We can't kill him,yet.
什么
What?
为什么？这无耻的东西跟你说什么了
Why not? What did this gut rot say to you?
我要把他带去给Trick
I need to take him to Trick.
不 Dyson 别！
No,Dyson no!
你觉得我不想把他的心挖出来吃给他看吗
You think I don't want to tear his heart out and eat it in front of him?!
我想，但是除了复仇我们还有别的事要担心
I do, but there are larger things at stake here than revenge.
Bo 求你了
Bo,please.
他会很痛苦的 Kenzi，Dyson会折磨他的
He will suffer Kenzi,Dyson will make sure of it.
不，你保证了的，你向我保证了他会死
No.You promised me. You promised me that he would die!
但要是Massimo知道什么能帮上忙的
But if Massimo has information that can help us...
你背叛了我，现在Dyson也背叛了我
First you betray me, now Dyson betrays me.
Dyson爱你
Dyson loves you.
不
No.
Kenzi 我们要信任他
Kenzi,we have to trust him!
Rainer，流浪者，混蛋，不管你叫啥
Rainer,Wanderer,Asshole,whatever your name is.
你肯定在这里面
You have got to be in here somewhere.
历史保留了任何人任何事的记录
History keeps a record of everyone and everything.
特么怎么回事
What the hell?
嗨
Hello.
看那妖兽，纯粹邪恶
"Behold the demon beast, evil pure.
尖牙长角，谓之Rainer
Fanged teeth,horned...Him they call Rainer."
知道了
Gotcha.
千年之后，他将现世
"Thousand years shall be ended,he shall be unbound."
好的，深呼吸，别吓倒
Okay. Don't freak out. Don't freak out.
放肆发泄
"To wreak torment beyond comparison"
背叛异种
"and betray the Fae."
我就知道，我……
I knew it. I...
你以为Una Mens挂掉了
You think because the Una Mens went tits up
事情就解决了？
that things'll just fall into place?
不，我们得介入
No. We need to intervene.
Bo和这个流浪怪人，他们干掉了Una Mens
Bo and this Wanderer freak...they took out the Una Mens.
大概还有扎莫拉的继承人
Probably the heir of Zamora too.
他们来找你我的麻烦只是时间问题
It's a matter of time before they come after me,after you.
要是那淫妖死了，一切都好办
Everything would be easier if the Succubus was dead.
Bo
Bo.
Evony，你可不能杀我的孙女
Evony,you're not going to kill my granddaughter.
你和你那家庭的执念
You and your obsession with family.
关于她我早就警告过你了
I warned you about her from the start.
听着，我为了这个连Hale的默哀日都没去
Look,I've missed Hale's Day of Silence for this
就不要浪费时间了行吗
so let's make it worth my while.
对，海妖
Ah yes,The Siren.
挺墨守成规的一个人，对吧
Bit of a stick in the mud,wasn't he?
他比我们俩都适合当领袖
He was a better leader than either of us will ever be.
说到Rainer，我们要想怎么对付他吗
Speaking of Rainer. Shall we figure out what to do with him?
首先从现在起我们得求同存异
First we have to put our differences aside.For now.
好吧，一点乐趣都没
Alright,but that's no fun.
Rainer Massimo说你快死了
Rainer,Massimo said that you're dying.
但我觉得有人知道是怎么回事
But I think someone has the answer.
Rosette，她曾是我最优秀的副将
Rosette...she was my best lieutenant.
用尽全力想要救我们下火车
Spent every moment trying get us off that train.
可我失败了，陛下
And I failed you,sir.
不
No.
说不定你现在可以帮我们
Well maybe you can help us now.
你不停嘟囔的那些预言
All these prophecies that you keep spouting,
有哪个说到Rainer的死吗
is there anything about Rainer dying?
那是不可能的
That would be impossible.
你俩的结盟会保证
The alliance between you both would have assured
那尘世的诅咒被解除
that the earthly curse was lifted.
什么尘世诅咒，什么结盟
What earthly curse? What alliance?
要是流浪者被救了，第一道诅咒就会失败
"If The Wanderer is rescued,and the first curse should fail"
他会被再次诅咒
"he shall be cursed again."
踏上尘世七日后就会痛苦而死
"To suffer and perish within seven days of being on this Earth."
妈的，他都来了六天了
Crap.He's been here six days.
以防首重诅咒被破解
So in case the first curse was broken
诅咒他的人又加了个双保险
a fail-safe was built in by the person who cursed him.
Trick
Trick.
只有你敌人的血才能破除这诅咒
And only by the blood of your enemy can the curse be broken.
我身上流着Trick的血
Trick's blood is in me.
我的家庭血统到底是怎么搞的
What is it with my family and blood?
那么我们可以破除这个诅咒
So we can break the curse.
说不定还能找到Pyrippus
And maybe find this Pyrippus.
那个一直在操纵我的人
The one that's been manipulating me.
找到他，老娘可要狠揍他一顿
The one whose ass I'm going to kick when I find him.
那怎么办
Which is how?
我们需要你和Rainer共有的东西
We need something that both you and Rainer shared.
一个标志，一个线索
A symbol, a clue.
是有那么个东西
There is one thing.
也就是说为了Rainer本日内不死
So to keep Rainer from dying in the next twenty-four hours,
为了找到这个搞乱我们生活的Pyrippus
and to find the Pyrippus that's screwing with all of our lives,
我们得正式结盟
we need to officially form an 'allegiance' and our
但我们唯一的线索就是这张塔罗牌
only clue is this tarot card.
塔罗牌的目的是指引
The purpose of a Tarot Card is to guide
所以里面大概有个线索
so perhaps there's a message in it.
是的，当Kenzi摸了这牌后
Yeah. The card revealed itself as a ticket
它烧起来了 变成了车票
when Kenzi touched it and it burned.
还是用老办法吧
Then we go old school.
MMXV 2015
MMXV 2015.
在Kenzi身上也发生了同样的事
The same thing happened to Kenzi!
这是时间，晚上8点15分
It's a time. 8:15.
或者是别的什么，一个暗号，或者日期
Or it could be something different. A code or a date.
也可能是地图上的坐标
It could be cartography coordinates.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
尖牙，长角？
Fangs,horns?
这个流浪者肯定不是现在在我厨房里那位吧
Obviously this Wanderer is not the guy in my kitchen.
这书看上去好假，墨水还没干呢
This book doesn't even look real. Is the ink still wet?
我也觉得奇怪，但是你想想
That confused me too. But look, then I
Rainer最开始什么也不记得了对吧
remembered, there was no memory of Rainer. Right?
好吧
Okay.
他的记忆一回来，历史对他的记忆
When his memory returned, history's memory of him
也回来了，可不是什么好东西
returned as well. And it's not pretty.
看看，战士将逃脱他的诅咒
Look."The Warrior shall escape his curse."
Valkyrie将要重生
"The Valkyrie shall be reborn."
扎莫拉族流血牺牲
"The blood of a Zamoran shall be spilled."
听起来熟悉吗
Any of this sound familiar to you?
驷马女人将会出现
"The women of the horse shall rise."
不知道是什么意思
I don't have any idea what that means.
战士和皇后之间
"Between the Warrior and the Queen"
有一个将会死去
"one of the two shall die."
我还不知道皇后是谁但是
I haven't determined who this queen is but...
恩，他们觉得是我
Yeah,they think it's me.
天啊Bo，那么这确实是真的了
Holy shit Bo. Then it's coming true,
你不觉得我们得把你从这弄出去吗
don't you see we have to get you out of here.
我们到底在干嘛
Why are you doing this?
有什么事会发生在你身上，而M女王
Something is coming for you. The Morrigan...
要报复我?
To get back at me?
我和黑暗派在一起是为了你
I stayed with the Dark for you.
什么
What?
我为了你与世隔绝
I isolated myself for you.
这都是为了你，我所做的一切都是为了你
This was all for you ...everything that I do is for you.
可你没告诉我你的计划，或者事实真相！
Except tell me your plan, or the truth!
我必须要瞒过你
I had to make you believe it,
不然M女王就会有所察觉了
if I was going make The Morrigan believe it.
哦，我现在不想听这个
Oh. I can't even hear this right now.
太多事情在发生了
There's too much going on!
Kenzi痛不欲生的时候你在哪
Kenzi is hurting so badly and where were you?
在黑暗派档案馆里找资料
Playing around in the Dark archives digging up shit
了解和我命运相交的那个男人
on the man somehow intertwined with my destiny.
所以就这样了 你选择了他是吧
So that's it. Hm? You choose him.
不是那样的
It is not like that.
我选的是你，但你伤透了我的心
I chose you...and you broke my heart.
只等你了，Bo
Whenever you're ready, Bo,
我觉得我发现了什么
I think I've figured something out.
我三个月前就预约了Serge
I booked Serge three months ago
老娘的下面又不会自己脱毛
and this puss-puss isn't gonna wax itself
我才不管他妈病成啥样了，你给我搞定就行了
so I don't care how sick his mother is, you make it happen.
Lauren
Lauren.
就像在自己家一样
Make yourself at my home.
我们在庆祝
We're celebrating.
是吗，天哪，医生，你干嘛了
We are? Heavens,doctor,what did you do?
发现了什么新孢子吗
Discover a new spore?
我想要正式加入黑暗派
I want to join the Dark.Officially.
恩
Hmm...
你可不会随便改变主意
Changes of heart don't happen for no reason.
我是异种世界里的人类
I'm a human in a Fae world.
长久以来，很难适应
Something that's been difficult to reconcile over the years.
我觉得脆弱渺小
Something that's made me feel weak and small.
是你给了我力量和自信
And you've given me strength, confidence.
噢，你不会是爱上我了吧
Oh,you're not falling in love with me,are you?
你知道吗，光明派囚禁了我
You know,The Light kept me imprisoned.
他们让我戴着条狗链样的项链
They made me wear a dog collar disguised as a necklace.
黑暗派却给了我尊重和自由
The Dark gave me me respect,freedom.
信任我参与他们的研究
They trusted me with their research.
你都能给相扑选手推销尿布了
You could sell diapers to a Sumo.
你知道吗，我现在觉得史无前例的更像我自己
Do you know that...I feel more like myself than I have in years.
你愿意认领我吗
Will you claim me?
亲，我根本不需要上你就可以支配你
Honey,I don't need to claim your clam to claim you.
你不如说说到底这是为了什么
Why don't you tell me what this is really about?
真心话？我无处可去
Truth? I have nowhere else to go.
我又没说让你当我女朋友
Look,I'm not asking you to be my girlfriend.
但我想要点女朋友的福利
But I might want some of the benefits.
你们人类真是莫名其妙
I have never understood you humans.
但是玩起来却有趣
But you are fun to play with.
驷马女人
The women of the horses.
欢迎，我是Epona修女
Welcome.I am Sister Epona.
你在找什么 孩子
What is it you seek,children?
退回来，皇后！
My Queen,stand back!
Rosette，退下
Rosette! Stand down.
就是这人在路上攻击了我
This is the one that attacked me when I arrived in your world.
我从来没见过这妹子
I've never seen this girl in my life.
你比我想像的还漂亮
You are more beautiful than I expected.
马是怎么回事
What's with the horse?
马
The horse.
那伟大全能的
The great and all-powerful.
支配生死的
With dominion over life and death.
只有全能无上的那人才能理解堕落的价值
Only the mighty one will denote the worthy from the fallen.
但要是你找到了
But if you find it...
找到什么
Find what?
你的血会毁了他，他必须得到保护
Your blood will destroy him. He must be protected.
保护不受谁的侵害
Protected from who?
那淫妖，你
The Succubus. You.
我怎么了
What about me?
女儿的动机不明
The daughter's intentions are unclear.
女儿？
Daughter?
Pyrippus，他是
The Pyrippus,is he...?
是你的父亲
Your father.
那我们要怎么办亲
So,what should we do then darling?
我提议，我们喝个烂醉，然后
My vote,we get rip-roaring drunk and settling into a stack
看看Rachel McAdams之类的电影
of oh I dunno, something Rachel McAdams-y
*演员  曾出演<时间旅行者的妻子>等片*
我可没叫你来卿卿我我，我要复仇
I didn't call you for cuddles Vex. I need to get revenge.
哦，很好，复仇可是我的中间名
Oh. Absolutely. Revenge is my middle name.
好吧，是另外个中间名，在Chauncey之后的那个
Well,second middle actually.After Chauncey.
*Chauncey也有比别人都好之意*
别批评，是家里人起的
It's a family thing,don't judge.
我说的是流血，肠子，痛苦，我说的是报仇
I'm talking blood spilled,guts,pain.I'm talking payback.
别说了，我都硬了
Stop.You're givin' me a stiffy.
好了告诉Vex叔叔，这该死的人是谁
Alright,tell uncle Vex,who's the unfortunate sot that's going
这马上就要死的人是谁
to met his untimely end?
他叫Massimo
His name is Massimo.
哦，那个低级无耻的人类德鲁伊？
Oh,well.That low level teabag human druid?
他到底怎么杀了Hale的
How in the world did he manage to kill Hale?
他有扎莫拉的圣枝
He had the twig of Zamora.
哪个白痴给他的
What stupid idiot gave that to him?
我
Me.
你知道你对付的是什么吗
Do you have any idea what you're dealing with?
你知道他在哪
You know where he is?
我当然知道，他就被关在下面
I know exactly where he is,in The Lair.
你是唯一一个能帮我的人了，来吧
And you are the only one  that can help me.So come on.
你知道你现在把我放在什么位置上吗
Listen,you're putting me in a real fix here, you understand?!
诚实可不是我的强项，你知道的亲
Honesty's not my strong suit,you know that,love.
我不是个好异种，要不给别人找麻烦，要不被人找麻烦
I'm not a good Fae.Screw or be screwed.
你忽然良心发现还是怎么的
You're having a crisis of conscience now?
Vex，老娘要的是真的你
Vex,I need the real you.
杀手，扭曲的，自大的肮脏的Vex
Killer,crooked,cocky,dirty-to-the-death Vex.
好吧好吧
Okay,okay.
我们要把这个傻逼Massimo除掉，但是
We'll take out this crumpet muncher,Massimo.But ...
让我来对付他，好吗
let me handle him,alright?
我会在instagram上给你贴细节的
I'll Instagram you every gratuitous little bloody tick.
用我最喜欢的开尔文滤镜，好吧
In Kelvin 'cause it's my favourite filter. Alright... ?
*instagram上一种滤镜*
不 Vex，我知道你想保护我
No! Vex, I know you're trying to protect me
但那无耻之人杀了我未来的丈夫
but that insect killed my almost husband.
他扼杀了我的幸福和未来，所以我得亲手来
He took my happiness, and my future,so this one is mine!
好吧
Alright.
这个我不能碰的东西是什么
What is this thing I'm not supposed to get my hands on?
和你爹又有什么关系
And what does it have to do with your father?
我的Dawning里面我看到匹马
In my dawning,I saw a horse.
就在我爸抱着婴儿时的我的房间里
In the room where my father held me as a baby.
去年旋转木马的影像总是出现在我脑海里
Last year I was haunted by visions of a carousel.
那都是线索，他想要见你
They were all clues.He wants to meet you.
他之前可没有
Well he never has before.
我这辈子都想见他，可我现在却好害怕
I've been waiting to meet him my whole life and now I am terrified.
因为大家所说的关于他的邪恶之事
Because terrible things have been said about him?
肯定有原因的
For a reason.
我也听说
So I have heard.
他要是邪恶 我的一部分肯定也是邪恶
If he is evil then a part of me must be evil as well.
看看历史书怎么说我的吧
Come on.Look at how the history books painted me
邪恶又堕落，野兽
malevolent and depraved.A beast.
历史就是喜欢书写丑陋之事
History really likes the ugly.
我的皇后，我必须告诉你，根据预言
My Queen,I must tell you...according to the prophecy
你和Rainer结盟会把你父亲从监狱里释放出来
your alliance with Rainer will release your father from his prison.
他被囚禁了
He's imprisoned?
为什么？谁干的？
Why? By who?
我不知道怎么办了
I don't know what to do.
我们要是结盟，你会活下去，我父亲却会出来
If we align,then you will live but my father will be released.
你对他一无所知，可能会面临前所未有的危险
And because you know nothing about him, the danger may be too great.
你看上去真是一团糟
You buggered up big style.
肯定很可怕吧
It must have been horrifying.
从那烈火中苟活就会变这样
To know what an ugly monster you'd be if you survived that fire.
我的每寸皮肤都烧焦了，我还能闻到那恶臭
Every inch of my body was searing,I could smell the stench.
我的恶臭，烧焦的肉体和头发
My stench. Burning flesh and hair
一出现就蒸干的汗水
and sweat that burned the instant it appeared.
可我赢了
But I prevailed.
多谢你的男朋友
Thanks to your boyfriend.
我的未婚夫？
My fiancee?
更好了
Even better.
圣枝在哪
Where is the twig of Zamora?
不能告诉你
Oh,can't say.
我把你的舌头切下来
You'll understand the irony of that
那可就真的是不能说了
once I've cut out your pretty little tongue.
噢，Vexie
Ow. Vexie.
对不起了亲，这人归我
I'm sorry, love. But this hot mess is mine.
你的？这个神经病杀了Hale
Yours?! This psychopath killed our Hale!
我知道
I know!
可他妈遗弃了他
But his mum abandoned him,and
我起了血誓抚养他
I gave my blood oath to take him in.
他曾经在我脚下蜷缩着
I mean he used to curl up at my feet
拿叉子戳我的脚，可是，就像霉菌一样
then stab them with forks,but,like a fine mold
他总是在那
he grows on you.
我给你买了一铺子的德鲁伊草药破烂
I bought you your own shop of herbal druidic shite and still
你却还是老样子不知长进
you're nothing but aggro,you little muppet.
我特么烦透你们异种和你那血誓了
I'm so sick of you Fae and your blood oath bullshit!
你想知道烧焦的血肉是什么感觉吗
So you wanna feel what burning flesh feels like?
让我来
Let me deal.
我为你做了这么多，快滚吧
I do every thing else for you, so just get out
趁我还没改变主意
before I change my mind.
不！
No!
对不起 Kenz，可我们都有包袱对吧
I'm sorry,Kenz,but we all got our burdens to bear.
不
No...
真是像重变处女了一般
It's like being a virgin all over again.
Lauren，谁知道
Lauren,who knew?
恩医生进来了
Well the doctor is in.
恩，我刚才真这么说了
Uh,I can't believe I just said that.
哦
Oh.
什么
What?
盐，好多盐
Ew,salt.Ugh,so...so much salt.
你在出汗嘛 滚床滚得好就是这样
You're sweating.Good sex will do that.
不
No.
不是我
Not to me.
我可从来没这样
Never me.
为什么我觉得怪怪的
Why do I feel weird?
因为 Evony
Because Evony...
你被改造了
you've been transformed.
欢迎来到我的世界
Welcome to my world.
你是百分百的人类了
You're one hundred percent human.
你这是想要融化我
Are you trying to melt me?
真可爱
That's adorable.
怎么会
How?
我用了你的基因，制造出了改造你的血清
I used your own DNA to create the serum that transformed you.
什么血清
What serum?
噢，这么快就忘了
Ow, forgotten already?
二十分钟前你不是还在下面
It's only 20 minutes ago you were down there.
哦
Oh.
噢
你造吗，书上会写的
You know, books will be written about this.
当然了我会写第一本
I'll write the first one of course.
就叫“Lewis对付难搞Fae大法”吧
It'll be called The Lewis Solution For Difficult Fae.
草，怎么了这是？
Shit.Something's happening?
我鼻子上有东西，弄走啊
Something's on my nose. Get it off!
痒痒嘛 人类都会痒的
You have an itch. Humans do that.
嗯，人类对Bo来说是个弱点
Hm.Bo has a soft spot for humans.
她的不信任就会甩在一边了 就像她的内裤一样
Her distrust just falls away,as do her panties.
她会开始喜欢我的 会看见我们之间的好多共同点
She'll grow to like me,see that we have so much in common.
比如，我们俩明显谁都上
For example,both of us'll obviously screw anything.
嗷！   不好意思
- Ow.
- Sorry.
嗯其实我也没不好意思
You know, I'm not sorry.
我本来想扎你的但是...这样也管用
I was going to prick you, but...this works too.
嗯，这种重量级的试验
You know,an experiment of this
可能对你非常危险啊
magnitude could be very risky for you.
你的系统要么承受得起
Your system could accept the sudden
这些突然的变化
and all encompassing changes very well.
或者呢NOr？
或者
Or...
也可能承受不起
it could all wear off
你一个小时内就会挂掉
and you'll be dead within the hour.
这些什么命运的说法啊
All this talk of destiny.
Dyson 我真是四面楚歌
Dyson, I am being pulled in every direction,
我不知道怎么办
I don't know what to do.
我不知道Bo，这是你的事
I dunno Bo.This one is your call.
哦 Dyson
Oh Dyson,
我们这么做的是对的吗
did we do the right thing?
对Massimo吗
With Massimo?
Kenzi被伤得很深 我们让她失望了
Kenzi is hurting so badly and we let her down.
Trick最擅长藏好东西了
Trick's good at hiding the real stuff.
但是也没那么擅长
But not that good.
好了
Okay,
我们喝酒吧
let's drink.
喝一点来回忆起好事
A little to remember the good stuff
多喝点来忘记坏事
a lot to forget the bad.
你要开那个还是怎么？
You gonna open that or what?
这是扎莫拉家族法典
It's the Zamora family code.
虽然我不知道Hale干嘛给我
Although I don't know why Hale gave it to me.
复杂，勇气，力量，和美丽
Complexity, courage,strength, and beauty;
时刻记住你的职责
Mindful always of your duty;
为了骨肉之情和我们所爱
To ties of blood and those we love;
用温柔之手，鸽子之翼
With gentle hands, wings of a dove;
做好准备，时刻警惕，保持敏锐
Ready thyself, on guard, be keen.
这不太像首诗啊
It's not much of a poem.
这个在Hale还是孩子的时候激励过他
It inspired Hale when he was a child.
你们看见这个了不
Are you guys seeing this?
做好准备，时刻警惕，保持敏锐
"Ready thyself, on guard; be keen;
与我重聚，皇后
To reunite with me, The Queen."
好吧 你不是要押韵吗
Well, there's your rhyme.
扎莫拉的诗
Zamora poetry.
Rainer回归了
Rainer re-membered;
历史自己重写了
history re-writing itself.
接下来还要怎样啊
What's next?
嗒哒～
Ta-da.
我认识这个徽章
I know this crest.
这是Raina骑士的命令书上面的
It's from the Order of the Knights of Raina.
代表忠诚
It means loyalty.
对他们的皇后忠诚
To their queen.
不只是他们的皇后
Not just their queen.
是“那个”皇后
"The" Queen.
我在战场上收集灵魂的时候
When I was collecting souls on the battlefield;
知道了谁为谁卖命
knowing who served whom ...
我得熟记所有出现的徽章
I had to memorize every crest there ever was.
看见这个王冠是怎么悬在盾徽的上面的不？
See this crown, how it hovers over the coat of arms?
还有这只蜜蜂，是蜂王，一点不假
And the bee,the queen bee.Literally.
他们觉得我就是那个皇后
They think that I'm that queen.
不 Bo 远不止那样
No Bo, it's so much more than that.
这个“皇后”不仅仅代表“皇后”
"The Queen" doesn't just mean "The Queen".
Bo 这表示你就是那个人
Bo it means you're The One.
诶我已经给沃里克郡的一个朋友打了电话了
Hey.I've made a call to a friend,in Warwickshire.
*英格兰的一个郡*
Bill
Bill.
著名剧作家，人不错的
Famous playwright, nice guy.
我们要跟他一起在那里待到事情平息之后
We're gonna stay with him 'til things blow over.
航班已经订好了
Flight's are booked.
来吧，走人
So come one, let's go.
不行我现在不能走
No,no I can't leave now.
这个还没完成
Not until it's finished.
你把扎莫拉的继承人给杀了啊你这个不识好歹的小兔崽子
You killed the heir of Zamora,you unappreciative little shit.
难怪你麻麻不喜欢你了
No wonder your mummy didn't want you.
我要拿你怎么办啊，啊？Mo？
What am I gonna do with you,eh Mo?
你妈把你留给我的时候你才一丁点大
You were such a wee thing when your mum dropped you off with me.
我拼尽全力把你好好带大
I tried everything I could to raise you right.
我是没给你吃好吗
Didn't I feed you proper eh,
没言传身教吗
teach you everything I know?
但是还是不够对吧
It still wasn't good enough for you, is it?
每个小精神病患者都需要自己的麻麻
Every little psycho needs their mummy.
除了现在 我看我是你唯一的亲人了
'Cept now I think I'm all you've got left.
拜托了 Mo
Please Mo.
跟我去英格兰吧
Come to England with me.
就你跟我
Just you and me.
就像一直以来一样
As it's always been.
这就对了 这才是我的乖孩子
There ya go, that's my boy.
Bill挺可爱的
Bill's a lovely guy.
只是别跟他提哈姆雷特就行好不？
Just don't mention Hamlet to him. Alright?
他对结局无法释怀
He's obsessed with the ending.
就觉得应该是另一个样子
Thinks it should've gone another way.
走吧
Come on.
拜托
Please.
别接
No.
不会有好结果的
It's only going to end badly.
求你了Mo
Please,Mo.
跟Vexie走吧
Come with Vexie.
喂？
Hello?
你怎么花了这么长的时间？
What took you so long?
还有你的脸怎么了？
And what's wrong with your face?
简直就像光子嫩肤失败了一样
You look like a walking chemical peel gone wrong.
哦～
Ohhh.
别撅嘴嘛
Don't pout.
太没味了
So boring.
来吧
Come.
这是真的
It's true.
医生转变了你
the doctor has turned you.
我能听见你心脏在跳了
I can hear your heart beating.
你跟我，我们一样了
You and I we're the same.
都是人类，这不是很好吗
Both human.Isn't it wonderful?
恶心
Gross.
我们得赶快了好吗
We have to hurry alright
Lauren要是发现
because when Lauren finds out
是我给她发了短信而不是Bo
that I sent a text, not Bo
Bo又不在楼下她就会回来的
and Bo isn't downstairs she'll come back.
好吧，那就走吧
Fine, let's go then.
老娘浑身发痒而且我觉得我好像
I'm itchy everywhere and I think I might be
要迎来人生的第一个大姨妈了
getting my period for the first time.
这个包里最好有包治百病大补丸
There better be some miracle cure-all in that bag.
去他妹的迷迭香
Shitty-ass rosemary
延长头发用的金毛
some blonde's extension
*404中剪下来的Tamsin的头发*
还有劣质芭比藤制家具？
and bad barbie rattan furniture?
*装起源之种的盒子*
就这些？
That's it?
我发现了很强大的东西
I found something very powerful
这个会让一切都好起来的
and this is gonna make everything better.
相信我
Trust me.
我怎么能在这种时候
How can I trust an albatross
相信一个只会失败的挫人
so utterly fantastic at failing?
要你带个可爱的大学同学回来
Bring home a cute University pal.
没做到
Fail.
要你把淫妖的脑袋给我拿过来
Bring me the head of the Succubus.
没做到
Fail.
治好我眼睛
Fix my eye.
老娘现在看得到斑斑点点的
I still see spots.
老是当个让人失望的怪物
Always such a disappointing monster.
别那么叫我
Don't call me that.
我以前总以为你内心是个怪物
I always knew you were a monster on the inside
现在你总算表里如一了
but now you look like a monster on the outside too.
别这样，妈妈
Stop it, mother!
妈妈？！
Mother?!
认出什么没
Recognize anything?
我之前还偷偷祈祷这个
I was secretly hoping this thing
我不该去找的东西就放在显眼处
I'm not supposed to find would be easy to spot.
这里人太多一次刷不完啊
There are too many of them to fight at once.
我们分头行动吧
Let's spread out.
我就只看见马啊
All I see are horses.
入侵者！
Intruders!
你不太喜欢我是吧 马语者
You don't like me very much, do you horse-whisperer?
要是它来了，你就会带来死亡和毁灭
If it comes, you will bring death and destruction.
要是什么来了？
If what comes?
别玩花样，背叛者
Do not play games, betrayer of all.
你是在干涉命运
You are interfering with destiny.
错
No
我是终于面对命运了
I'm finally facing it.
哦你看着不舒服啊？
Ooh, does that bother you?
你只喜欢骑马
You only like horse-play when
因为你是骑的那人？
you're the one doing the playing?
你必须死！
You must die!
诶我们找到了，现在怎么办
Hey.We found it,now what?
小心点
Be careful.
可能是匹特洛伊木马
Could be a Trojan horse.
嗯
Yeah.
可能我们要找的东西就在这匹马里面
Maybe what we're looking for is inside the horse.
肯定有启动器之类的东西
There must be some kind of trigger or something.
等下
Wait!
做好准备 时刻警惕 保持敏锐 与我重聚
"Show thyself,on guard;be keen;To reunite with me
皇后
The Queen."
不要！
No!!!
是婚约，不可能
The handfasting. It cannot be.
婚约？
Handfasting?
啊不要不要不要
Oh no,no,no.
搞过了没兴趣
Been there,done that.
跟一只洛基在零星级尼亚加拉酒店里
With a Loki in a cheesy Niagara hotel.
啥？
What?
要是我搞错了你就说吧，但是
Tell me if I'm getting this wrong but
我们是不是要结婚啊？
are we supposed to get married?
Kenzi
Kenzi.
我很高兴你在这里
I'm glad you're here.
怎么样了啊
How have you been?
带你的新女骑士到处参观了没
Showing your new lady knight the sights?
你可以试着疏远我 Kenzi
You can try to push me away Kenzi
但是没有用的
but it's not gonna work.
我爱你
I love you.
真的好有意思啊
It's really interesting stuff.
一个眼睛时棕时蓝
One with eyes both brown and blue.
一个能变形，还有一只Valkyrie
One who shifts,a Valkyrie too.
一个的血能主宰世界
One with blood that rules the world
一个能唱歌，生命随风飘散
one who sings,his life unfurled.
一个战士为她引路，一个医治者总在她身边
A warrior to be her guide,a healer always by her side.
教授，还有Mary Ann
The professor and Mary Ann!
*喜剧Gilligan's Island中的人物*
除了那个弱爆的人类妹子其他人都在
Everyone's in here except the weak human girl.
Kenzi 你是我们大家的一部分啊
Kenzi,you are a part of all of us.
解除对我的认领 Bo
Unclaim me Bo.
这只是你闹情绪说的话
That is your grief talking.
你不是真的想这样
That's not what you want.
不是，我知道我不想再待在这里了
No I know I don't want to be here anymore.
我的皇后
My Queen.
现在没空
Not now.
是Rainer
It's Rainer.
没有多少时间了
There's not much time.
你能不能把这事给我做了
Can you just do this one thing?
我就要你做这么一件事
This one thing that I'm asking you!
不要
No.
我不要让你走 我做不到
I'm not letting you go. I can't.
这和你无关
This is not about you!
Kenzi 时间不合适啊
Kenzi this is a tough time.
解除，对我的认领
Unclaim me.
好
Fine.
我解除对你的认领
I unclaim you.
我的皇后，请吧
My Queen,please.
给，把这个给Rainer
Here,give this to Rainer.
抱歉，我只能做这么多了
I'm sorry.It's the best I can do.
Kenzi，我们还没说完
Kenzi,we are not done.
我们没可说的了
Yeah.We're done!
怪物
Monster!
好残忍
So cruel.
我恨你
I hate you!
可我爱你
But I love you.
Valkyrie的头发，种子
The Valkyrie hair,the seed?
怎样才能让你爱我
What will make you love me?!
傻瓜，白痴，蠢货
Stupid.Stupid.Stupid!
还有你，我会给她一切她想要的东西
And you,I will get her everything she wanted.
我会成为她期望的人
I will be everything she wanted.
你，你得帮我
And you,you're gonna help me.
我不会帮你的
I won't.
我们会合作很愉快的
We are gonna make a great team.
当然了，你会死的
Of course,you're gonna have to die...
我不会帮助疯子的
I will not help a madman.
我不是怪物
I'm not a monster!
不要叫我怪物
Stop calling me a monster!
等你看了我接下来要做的事
When you see what I'm about to do...it's...
你是个科学家
You're a scientist.
你真的一定会喜欢这个的
You are really,really gonna dig this.
这是起源之种
This is the Origin Seed.
种子，别，Massimo
The Seed.No,Massimo.
我干什么都行
I will do anything.
求你别吃那个
Please,please do not eat that.
谁吃了这种子
Whoever takes this seed will
就有了Una  Mens的联合之力
have the combined power of the Una Mens.
这就代表了不可阻挡的力量
And that means all power.
会成为我的
And it is all mine.
不不不，别啊
No,no,no,no,no...
恩
Mm-mmm.
不要啊
Please...
一接到你的纸条我就来了
I came as soon as I got your note.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我身边的一切都变了
Everything is changing around me.
我不能停止那些 可我能控制这事
I can't stop that,but I can control this.
我会和你绑定 救你的命
So I will bind with you and save your life
自行面对我的父亲
and face my father on my own terms.
你确定你要做这吗
Are you sure this is what you want?
我明说了 这和爱无关
Just to be clear.This isn't about love.
这是为了我的家庭
This is about what's right for my family.
Bo 为了异种一起战斗是我们的宿命
Bo,it is our destiny to fight together for the good of the Fae.
你我的结合就像是组队刷怪走任务
To unite will be to join in a mutual quest.
顺便说下 我确实爱你
And for the record,I do love you.
好了好开始吧
Here we go.
就这样了
Is that it?
你刚确实救了我的命
Well you did just save my life.
预言已被写下
The prophecy has been written.
她会崛起，那战士将成为她的士兵
"She will rise,with The Wanderer as her soldier"
他们会联手释放黑暗之王
"and together they will release the Lord of Darkness."
不好意思，你说啥
I'm sorry,what did you just say?
黑暗之王将从地狱重生
The Dark Lord rises from Hel.
他马上就会出现
He will be here any minute.
地狱的那个地狱？
Hell,hell?
*北欧神话中战死的英雄的灵魂去英灵殿  凡人的亡灵则去往地狱*
不，是英灵殿的镜像
No,the mirror of Valhalla.
Hel
H-E-L.
*Hel 北欧神话中的地狱，由Loki之女Hel掌管*
你背叛了我，贱人
You betrayed me, you bitch.
在我身边这么多年，都是诡计
All those years by my side...a ruse.
你会付出代价的
You will pay!
不，他会保护我
No.He will protect me.
他许诺了我一切
He promised me everything.
不灭的生命
Everlasting life.
我自己的力量
Power of my own.
他会来的
He will be here.
预言说他会来
The prophecy said he would come.
他在哪呢
So where is he then?
不，别
No...No!
求你了，不要
Please,please!
这都是为了你
It was all for you!
天啊，Rainer
Oh god,Rainer!
我们都干了什么
What have we done?